Aung Si Min Htet

Computer Vision Research Engineer

Address Jeonju, South Korea

Phone +821021751105

E-mail andy@jbnu.ac.kr

Aung is a dedicated Software Engineer with over five years of experience specializing in Java, Kotlin, and Python. As a graduate with a Master's Degree in Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence, Aung has an excellent research background in Computer Vision and Deep Learning, for which he has earned multiple Best Paper awards. He currently serves as a Computer Vision Research Engineer, using his hands-on experience with TensorFlow and PyTorch to transform complex research ideas into practical real-world applications. When he steps away from the keyboard, he's a passionate pianist, an amateur photographer, and an enthusiastic UI/UX designer.

Work History

2020-08 - 2023-08 Research Assistant

Software Engineering Lab, Jeonbuk National University

Researched on deep learning based computer vision projects and implemented the research ideas into industry-use software systems for end-users using end-to-end ML/DL pipelines.

2020-10 - 2021-04 Senior Software Engineer

ConceptX Myanmar

Responsible for developing scalable and high-performance native android applications using Java and Kotlin programming languages, as well as backend API services using PHP and Laravel framework.

2020-10 - 2021-04 UI/UX Designer

ConceptX Myanmar

Responsible for designing the user interface/user experience designs for android, iOS, and website with user-oriented, mobile-friendly and easy-to-access modern UI/UX design concepts.

2018-03 - 2019-12 Mobile Development Lead

Binary Tech

Managed small team of software engineers, and visual designers to develop and deliver several end-to-end mobile and web based software systems to meet various clients' business requirements. Developed and delivered more than 30 software development projects.

ETrade Myanmar

Responsible for creating and maintaining secure, mobile-responsive android applications for News and Telecom services using Java and C++.

Education

2020-09 - 2023-08 Master of Science: Computer Science And Artificial Intelligence

Jeonbuk National University

2013-09 - 2018-08 Bachelor of Science: Computer Science And Engineering

Dagon University

Research Projects

- Agricultural Crop Pests and Diseases Recognition using Self-supervised Incremental Learning
- Biometrics Palm Vein Segmentation and Recognition using Deep Learning for Personal Identification
- Pig Scale Smart Estimation using 3D Point Cloud and Machine Learning Algorithms

Awards

- 2022 Best Paper Award at 2022 Annual Conference of KIPS (ACK)
- 2021 Best Paper Award at 2021 International Conference on Computer Engineering and Artificial Intelligence (ICCEAI)
- 2020 Brain Korea Plus (BK21+) Scholarship
- 2019 Global Korea Scholarship (GKS)
- 2016 Korean Government Scholarship Program (KGSP)
- 2015 Grand Prize Winner at SAMSUNG Tech Institute Mobile Application Development Competition

Publications

Conference Papers

- A. S. M. Htet and H. J. Lee, "Strawberry Pests and Diseases Recognition with Self-supervised Learning," The 2023 World Congress in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, & Applied Computing (CSCE'23), 2023. (Accepted)
- **앤디** and 이효종. "생체 인식 인식 시스템을 위한 주의 인식 잔차 분할." 한국정보처리학회 학술대회논문집 29.2 (2022): 300-302.
- A. S. M. Htet and H. J. Lee, "Palm Vein Identification and Verification using Deep Metric Learning," The 2022 World Congress in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, & Applied Computing (CSCE'22), 2022.
- A. S. M. Htet and H. J. Lee, "TripletGAN VeinNet: Palm Vein Recognition Based on Generative Adversarial Network and Triplet Loss," 2021 International Conference on Computer Engineering and Artificial Intelligence (ICCEAI), 2021, pp. 454-458.

Journal Publications

- A. S. M. Htet and H. J. Lee, "Contactless Palm Vein Recognition Based on Attention-Gated Residual U-Net and ECA-ResNet." Applied Sciences 13.11 (2023): 6363.
- A. S. M. Htet and H. J. Lee, "Palm Vein Segmentation and Verification using Modified U-Net Model." Journal of Information Processing Systems (2023). (Accepted)

Technical Skills

Java, Kotlin, Python, PHP, Laravel, Javascript, C++, C#, Matlab, Tensorflow, Pytorch, UI/UX Design

Languages

English, Korean, Burmese